DANIEL LAGO HUERTA

WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT ME

Cel. 55 1288 - 3754

Mail: daniel-alh@hotmail.com

Github: Daniel-lago

PROFILE

I'm a 25 years old, enthusiast of web develop technologies, managment, and another fields that can help me to improve my understanding of the world.

Team-oriented with a positive attitude and a fit in any fast-paced, inclusive culture, fast-learning and feedback readiness.

WEB DEVELOP SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS₃,
- · JavaScript,
- jQuery,
- Bootstrap,
- Express.is.
- · React.js,
- Database MongoDB, MySQL,
- React,
- Git

WORK EXPERIENCE

REGIONAL SALES DIRECTOR

OPPO MEXICO | MARCH 2020 - FEBRUARY 2021

- Responsible for leading sales teams to reach sales targets.
- Hiring and training team members, setting quotas, evaluating and adjusting performance, and developing processes that drive sales
- Youngest Region Director (23) in Mexico Team.

IT ANALYST

COMPUCOM WYNDHAM DESTINATIONS || FEBRUARY 2019 - AUGUST 2019

- Supporting end users from Wyndham Destinations company in issues related with our IT Services.
- Fixing technical issues for customers based mainly on USA, Canadá, India and UK.

LANGUAGUES

ENGLISH - FLUENT

GERMAN - INTERMEDIATE

SPANISH - NATIVE

EDUCATION

INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS BACHELOR DEGREE

INSTITUTO POLITÉCNICO NACIONAL - ESCA | 2015 - 2019

INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS - INTERNATIONAL STUDENT EXCHANGE

UNIVERSIDAD SANTO TOMÁS - BOGOTÁ, COL | 2019

QUALIFICATIONS

WEB DEVELOPER FULLSTACK BOOTCAMP

TECNOLÓGICO DE MONTERREY X TRILOGY EDUCATIONS FEB - AUG 2022

PROJECT MANAGMENT FUNDAMENTALS

GOOGLE X COURSERA

AUG-SEP 2022